http://usa.hudsonreed.com/privacy

Menu
ShowersShower Systems & Shower FaucetsAll Shower Systems & Faucets1-Outlet Shower Systems2-Outlet Shower Systems3-Outlet Shower SystemsShower PanelsShower Heads & ArmsAll Shower Heads & ArmsShower Heads with ArmsShower HeadsHandheld Shower HeadsExposed Pipe Shower KitsBody Jets & SpraysShower ValvesAll Shower Valves1-Outlet Shower Valves2-Outlet Shower Valves3-Outlet Shower ValvesExposed Shower ValvesShower SeatsOutdoor ShowersShower AccessoriesFaucetsAll FaucetsBathroom Sink FaucetsTub FaucetsKitchen FaucetsShop by CollectionSinksBathtubsBathroom VanitiesRadiatorsAll RadiatorsAll RadiatorsVertical RadiatorsHorizontal RadiatorsTraditional RadiatorsWhite RadiatorsAnthracite RadiatorsDesigner RadiatorsAll Designer RadiatorsVertical Designer RadiatorsHorizontal Designer RadiatorsWhite Designer RadiatorsAnthracite Designer RadiatorsBlack Designer RadiatorsTraditional RadiatorsAll Traditional RadiatorsVertical Traditional RadiatorsHorizontal Traditional RadiatorsWhite Traditional RadiatorsRaw Metal Traditional Radiators4-Column Traditional RadiatorsElectric RadiatorsRadiator Valves & AccessoriesTowel WarmersAll Towel WarmersAll Towel WarmersDesigner Towel WarmersTraditional Towel WarmersWhite Towel WarmersChrome Towel WarmersHydronic Towel WarmersAll Hydronic Towel WarmersWhite Towel WarmersChrome Towel WarmersFlat Towel WarmersCurved Towel WarmersTraditional Towel WarmersElectric Towel WarmersTowel Warmer Valves & AccessoriesSaleInformation Center
Account
100% Secure ShoppingMoney Back GuaranteeFree Shipping*10 Year Warranty
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Hudson Reed uses and protects any information that you give Hudson Reed when you use this website.
Hudson Reed is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Hudson Reed may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
What we do with the information we gather
Security
How we use cookies
Links to other websites
List of cookies we collect
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
your name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as your zip code, preferences and interests
other information that is relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
A full list of cookies we collect can be found here.
Back to top
What we do with the information we gather
This information is needed so that we can understand customer needs, improve our service and for the following reasons:
internal record keeping
improving products and services
we may periodically send promotional emails about products and special offers, using the email address you have provided
we may occasionally contact you for market research purposes. You may be contacted by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use any information gathered to customise the website according to customer interests.
Back to top
Security
Hudson Reed is fully committed to ensuring your personal information is kept secure. We have implemented appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online, and to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure.
Back to top
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. If you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps to analyse web traffic or informs you when you visit a particular website. Cookies also allow web applications to respond to you as an individual, tailoring its operation to suit your needs, likes and dislikes, by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
Usa.hudsonreed.com uses traffic log cookies to identify which website pages are being used. This helps us to analyse data about web traffic and improve our website. This information is used solely for statistical analysis purposes. The data is then removed from the system.
Cookies enable us to monitor which pages our customers find useful and which they don’t, helping us to provide you with a better website and shopping experience. They do not give us access to your computer or any other information about you, other than that which you choose to share with us. You can choose whether to accept or decline the use of cookies on your browser. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but this setting can be altered if you so wish. Do be aware that declining cookies prevent you taking full advantage of the Hudson Reed website.
Back to top
Links to other websites
The Hudson Reed website may contain links to other websites of interest. If you use these links to leave our site, please be aware that we do not have any control over the content of that website and cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information you may provide whilst visiting such sites. These website are not governed by this privacy statement. We recommend that you exercise caution and view the privacy statement applicable to the website in question before submitting any information.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of the personal information you provide in the following ways:
when you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for and check the box which indicates that you do not want the information to be used for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously given your consent for your personal information to be used in this way, you may change your mind at any time. Write to us or email info@hudsonreed.com
Hudson Reed will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties without your permission, or unless we are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you third party promotions that we feel may be of interest to you, if you tell us that you want this to happen.
Back to top
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Back to top
MY ACCOUNTHelpSign InABOUT USContact UsTermsAbout UsDelivery & ReturnsPayment MethodsCookiesPrivacy PolicyBlogBTU CalculatorSitemap
SocialFacebookTwitterPinterestYouTubeBlogHouzz
Newsletter
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Subscribe
© Hudson Reed 2020
Our 128-bit encryption keeps your personal data secure.
Our website uses cookies to give you the best experience of our site.
By using this site, you agree to the use of cookies.
Read our policy.
I agree
